<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Poliwat brainDump</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Poliwat brainDump</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Pale Blue Dot Fm</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 10:29:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3pac 0hoots Bonny View</title>
      <link>/post/3pac-0hoots-bonny-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 10:29:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/3pac-0hoots-bonny-view/</guid>
      <description>YOGO by POLIW.AT 1032AM
@ bonny view myfav room the window one, jordan is here he just got up
http://www.theexit.org/reviews/
^^ james was telling me @ NB to get reviews running on our site - we need people to review our plays funCheap SF
Two plays under my belt but don&#39;t act it  this is julia&amp;rsquo;s dead brother holy crap so funny
 703pm
telescope
time
out of line</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Как Долго Перо Мусикал</title>
      <link>/post/%D0%BA%D0%B0%D0%BA-%D0%B4%D0%BE%D0%BB%D0%B3%D0%BE-%D0%BF%D0%B5%D1%80%D0%BE%D0%BC%D1%83%D1%81%D0%B8%D1%86%D0%B0%D0%BB/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 11:17:40 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/%D0%BA%D0%B0%D0%BA-%D0%B4%D0%BE%D0%BB%D0%B3%D0%BE-%D0%BF%D0%B5%D1%80%D0%BE%D0%BC%D1%83%D1%81%D0%B8%D1%86%D0%B0%D0%BB/</guid>
      <description>She sitting pretty but new fad that JS framework by POLIW.AT 1118am
there&amp;rsquo;s not enough time in the world
the toe is toeing up
on stage falling harder than I should&#39;ve fallen using a toe to tell the time will be a timeless memory memory I now need don&#39;t want to smoke weed is this a new me reminds me of new leaf supplement section when a pregnant lady said it&#39;s a new different this my new alternative medicine to indifference when you care about something so much is it worth the risk is it worth the fitness required as is a marathon, not a sprint required as is and never some summer bod that never happens love as is as if it were the last moment so I&#39;m on stage falling harder than I should&#39;ve fallen now my wrist is swollen blood was drawn but this pawn don&#39;t mind cause I&#39;m on stage falling harder than I should&#39;ve fallen   258PM just had a nice long walk to food and a park in noes with cam gus ted marina olivia rose dennis chris and we met nate there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trapt as Fred Laser Therapy</title>
      <link>/post/trapt-as-fred-laser-therapy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 13:34:06 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/trapt-as-fred-laser-therapy/</guid>
      <description>Pale Blue intros by POLIW.AT 134PM
omg i left my clothes at the locker in the theatre and they don&amp;rsquo;t open up again until tuesday.
so I&amp;rsquo;m only in my fred outfit with the red jumper and cam&amp;rsquo;s pants he wore when he got the job at ebay.
jacks&amp;rsquo; about to be here, Im at cam&amp;rsquo;s&amp;rsquo; apartment by myself. Everyone went to Marina&amp;rsquo;s for bagels but chris and I were too tired</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who I Post To</title>
      <link>/post/who-i-post-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 05:43:05 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/who-i-post-to/</guid>
      <description>Lexapro TB by POLIW.AT 5 somethiing AM
 toe blue play done cast party all night lovely brits annoying brits too fucked up to tell the difference
who do I post make to i remember when i had a really good thyme it was very fruitful, just cuz if who knew knew I knew they knew then it wouldn&#39;t be hard to find post even a pigeon gets it no diss needed vague my only if you wanna make fun of people you need to talk to sam and sam only he&#39;s the best at making fun of people saturated in s god damn s no one knows the difference matter of time its the trickle down effect no one even bothers even when I spell it I&#39;m faithful of the trickle only a matter of time before the king gets abandoned for some better lute shallow depth as a front brute et tu as if you won the hoot patience that a virtue I told you when I wanted to ammend it I&#39;m done with the play and the play is haunting me I can&#39;t quit the play now that there isn&#39;t an excuse to spend so much time together so where do I post to when I can&#39;t even write the post who do I scream to when I couldn&#39;t get the vote Who will I become through chasing your soul why don&#39;t I care if you hurt me and go a moment with you is enough of the world the body mind and spirit yes, I said a moment with you and enough of this world why spend so much time on something bad who told me I&#39;d live this long without feeling this bad who killed Seinfeld a line I always fuck up nothing gets me out of head space to crawl up theres no ammount of weed that could fuck me up harder than this holy dance break it off two days ago you crazy pants freestyle with naked guy with sunglasses in canon in the bathub do I feed her ego or feed anyone fishing for a compliment listening to tunes I made I done m.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poetics 2 WithArthur</title>
      <link>/post/poetics-2-witharthur/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2019 09:45:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/poetics-2-witharthur/</guid>
      <description>945AM
@ firefly w/ Briconomu .
bout to hit the 17 then the caltrain then the bart then walk to jack&amp;rsquo;s in Oakies
-=-=- often -=-=- 1015AM
on 17 - listening to bonjo mila marion mom and dad at the santa barbara zoo, all jamming on one of their mallet instruments outside. part of the chill poliwat playlist. nice and calming.
bumping jimmothy leary
just saw him at safeway last night, we&amp;rsquo;re going to hang the second I&amp;rsquo;m done with the play basically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valentines Day Media M0nk</title>
      <link>/post/valentines-day-media-m0nk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Feb 2019 12:54:01 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/valentines-day-media-m0nk/</guid>
      <description>Banking on trainlate for mom&amp;#39;s bday by POLIW.AT 1254
just got downtown to tabby cat coffee with Briconomu
power went out last night
I read her arthur C clark the sequel to 2001 - she hadn&amp;rsquo;t seen the movie though.
fuji slept over and he gave me a secret bump of coke right when I woke up we kept between us.
then Briconomu made preworkout pink drinks from I think costco and now we have coffee - the mocha java so I&amp;rsquo;m feeling pretty good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books Money and Me</title>
      <link>/post/books-money-and-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2019 12:12:10 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/books-money-and-me/</guid>
      <description>1212PM
DMT type beat by POLIW.AT books money and me.
@ SC roasters.
books god damn. let&amp;rsquo;s start with books. I can&amp;rsquo;t find Homo Deus Briconomu got me, so I just have Walden.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing in it though.
money I have a quarter. I had a dollar that actually I got from a homeless lady on haight street. Today is totally devoted to getting some work. I&amp;rsquo;m going to send Sean a video asking for help in employment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Due Diligence</title>
      <link>/post/due-diligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 08:23:59 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/due-diligence/</guid>
      <description>I am soup by POLIW.AT  838am its time at the bonnu djy
130pm
me jack helen are all working on campus today lol - they are visiting from the city :D
I&#39;m confused tonight living in a van living with some cheap rent living with musician friends god damn and I know that love and legacy will feed my soul in the end baby I talking more songs I talking I plead the fifth who I make love to or what about when I spit god damn I don&#39;t care about hits I will die but my ideas won&#39;t bitch  249pm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homo Deus Bonny View RR</title>
      <link>/post/homo-deus-bonny-view-rr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 12:17:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/homo-deus-bonny-view-rr/</guid>
      <description>Addy Daddy type beat by POLIW.AT 1219PM
homo deus
in my favorite room this is the one lol&amp;hellip;..
the sun room on the deck
listening to freestyles from last night, writing down the nugs.
``` the first line of it acid confession I said are you making a pass at me we were high up up in the tree big moonlight out up at an airbnb tight it was just a field a pond a river we explored it all she didn&#39;t want to go in the water I went and splashed her uh oh they are missing and I know that oh miss myself missin you think about it in the river though that was a little piece of old me shut it down I feel it like it was yesterday time stops when I&#39;m with you as of late how long before it goes away damn from plan z to plan a holy shit and the england kinda girl england she rom baths too phoebe yeah shit loved it same thing thats what love do at the end of the day they&#39;re just waitresses waiting to die in this nation I never wouldve predicted it but then we went I fucking just cheated I just fucking lost it cam&#39;s couch ted&#39;s bed and climbing through jack&#39;s window ```  0i09</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Higher Than a Last Picnic</title>
      <link>/post/higher-than-a-last-picnic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 14:37:57 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/higher-than-a-last-picnic/</guid>
      <description>239pm
higher than a picnic in bob&amp;rsquo;s room. i was just typing my password instead of the word false on changing the variable.
I don&amp;rsquo;t want to write about it but I have to get it out
so I&amp;rsquo;ll green text it
lryics 4 days  1039PM
Made it to bonny dojo but brianna left though but bob&#39;s wife found my malachite free lsd bad trip best band tonight trippy chris gave me a cd like now we friends for life freestyle till I die songbird every day that&#39;s a beautiful life  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Premiere of Poetics 2</title>
      <link>/post/premiere-of-poetics-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 09:41:46 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/premiere-of-poetics-2/</guid>
      <description>949AM
its been so hectic upon waking!
@ ted gus&amp;rsquo;s - their dad came over so we power cleaned real wquick.
I woke up with a sore throat so it looks like Im getting sick? but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter much because I have so much adrenaline. I&amp;rsquo;m dressed as Fred right now, which is 100% cameron&amp;rsquo;s interview outfit that got him a job at Ebay.
I feel more like Fred.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Play Promotion as a Monk and Matt Stole the Couch</title>
      <link>/post/play-promotion-as-a-monk-and-matt-stole-the-couch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 07:24:25 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/play-promotion-as-a-monk-and-matt-stole-the-couch/</guid>
      <description>My friends fatal flaws master list by POLIW.AT 725AM
I don&amp;rsquo;t mind that he stole the couch just now - I had it all night and got the proper amount of zs.
Philip S H Hour | I&amp;rsquo;m thinking of you.
I have green snot which might be me getting sick. You can&amp;rsquo;t get sick Michael, because the play premieres tomorrow night. I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to perform. Then the next night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hope Im Wrong</title>
      <link>/post/hope-im-wrong/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2019 08:58:04 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hope-im-wrong/</guid>
      <description>858AM
woke up and couldn&amp;rsquo;t fall asleep in the middle of the night last night.
Climate Optimism by POLIW.AT had this weird pit in my stomach
like a family member died
and jack and helen got mad ay my typing so I went back to bed
and silently cried. I imagined it being my dad first, then my mom, then although it&amp;rsquo;s more likely my grandma third. I could only tell myself I hope I&amp;rsquo;m wrong over and over again and eventually drifted off into sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crossing the Rubicon Threshold Changed My Tastes</title>
      <link>/post/crossing-the-rubicon-threshold-changed-my-tastes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 10:09:28 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/crossing-the-rubicon-threshold-changed-my-tastes/</guid>
      <description>1009 AM Bipolar Mixed Features Type Beat by POLIW.AT In oakland at jack&amp;rsquo;s house.
Who is to blame
1055AM
welcome to humanity where the best sex is to be found in the poor, the passionate, and the rich and smart many of the smartest seem to be dogs at heart  I wanted to wait until my dad died before I sucked a dick but that &amp;lsquo;ed&amp;rsquo; doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean I did it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Girls Missing Fingers My Fingers Missing Girls</title>
      <link>/post/my-girls-missing-fingers-my-fingers-missing-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 10:22:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/my-girls-missing-fingers-my-fingers-missing-girls/</guid>
      <description>BART workout type beat by POLIW.AT 110AM
https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=18470226
smelled great lo siento im sorry i hate jack i was just being normal to him and he caught me sniffing my finger cause i did it too many times NEW DEAL NO telling any jack anything im sorry u great no it makes it more real if someone bears to witness so people watching our play 4 times really immortalizes it for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poetics 2 Tech Rehearsal 1</title>
      <link>/post/poetics-2-tech-rehearsal-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 14:49:38 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/poetics-2-tech-rehearsal-1/</guid>
      <description>Poetics Vibes RehearseTape Mix 1 by POLIW.AT 250 pm
@ rehearsal, its the ale boys scene so I have a second to type.
Michael H and Marina just left, we&amp;rsquo;ve been practicing since 10 AM.
It&amp;rsquo;s funny, I feel I could be a lot more help to jack if he wasn&amp;rsquo;t being so horrible to me, but I don&amp;rsquo;t take it personally cause he&amp;rsquo;s being mean to everyone else. He&amp;rsquo;s just stressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hunter Is Throwing Up</title>
      <link>/post/hunter-is-throwing-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 13:36:03 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hunter-is-throwing-up/</guid>
      <description>Nerd Type Beat by POLIW.AT 502 PM
hunter threw up like 5 times but we&amp;rsquo;ll hang out for real soon.
Damn still recovering from falling in a damn khole on the first night of moving in!
there was a tub orgy situation but I was throwing up- not that I&amp;rsquo;d do that anyways, it felt like I was recieving surgery, but they were just stretching me out.
Was having a shitty day, briconomu&amp;rsquo;s being awesome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cement Head Mid Chess Game</title>
      <link>/post/cement-head-mid-chess-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 12:22:50 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/cement-head-mid-chess-game/</guid>
      <description>Cement Head mid chess game by POLIW.AT 1222pm
Friday !
Been up for about 30 min. We were up until about 7 AM. I threw up on Brianna and made her cum. After her and the girls took care of me and stretched me out on the deck I felt a lot better.
Apparently I was saying gibberish, I got a little too fucked up.
ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok ok</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving to Bonny Dojo</title>
      <link>/post/moving-to-bonny-dojo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 10:29:50 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/moving-to-bonny-dojo/</guid>
      <description>Weak words from a strong man by POLIW.AT 1029AM.Davis.CA
Briconomu and I are moving to SC today! She&amp;rsquo;s making paleo pancakes right now. Listening to Herbie Hancock.
I look
I&amp;rsquo;m moving the audio from the poetics rehearsals onto a recorder.
I gotta get cameron&amp;rsquo;s pws so I can bum off his servers for this site - an old client I don&amp;rsquo;t talk to anymore seems to have cancelled their getforge hosting with me so everything&amp;rsquo;s about to fall offline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Track I Just Lost My Cellphone</title>
      <link>/post/track-i-just-lost-my-cellphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 11:05:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/track-i-just-lost-my-cellphone/</guid>
      <description> Track I just lost my cellphone  I just lost my cellphone I just lost my cellphone you can call me on brianna&#39;s phone (ah) I just lost my cellphone you can call me on katie&#39;s phone you can call me on muneerah&#39;s phone you can call me on kenzie&#39;s phone you can call me on niko&#39;s phone you can call me on robin&#39;s phone v1 my cellphone I lost it I broke it I stole it you know this forgive it people who I care about people (talking) would you forgive me this iPhone graveyard behind me havent had a phone in months now Im thinking clearly  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Track Got a Lesson</title>
      <link>/post/track-got-a-lesson/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 10:57:08 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/track-got-a-lesson/</guid>
      <description>sucka for my tape
(ch-vamp) next time I got out I teach god a lesson next time I go out I teach god a lesson (v1) got a lesson from the drunk shaman mantra of a thousand as of late he my therapy today I need it I breath it a clean slate pero slate lake stop crying over lost tape a la carte trip visit from edo suddenly I a monk handsome youth having fun god chose my temple he chose the sword I chose the pen and his temple well tortured to death there&#39;s snow on his sleeve I&#39;ll make a plan to fuck for a living believe wouldn&#39;t you these discoveries my discoveries bother the bishop cause got a lesson from the woke hobo pro bono bonobo in periheral tho next time I go out I teach and leave a note (ch) next time I go out I teach god a lesson next time I go out I teach god a lesson next time I go out I teach god a lesson next time I go out I teach god a lesson (v2) father paul mark let me record ya&#39;ll chanting  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>36choR and Robin Read Us BJ Novak</title>
      <link>/post/36chor-and-robin-read-us-bj-novak/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jan 2019 09:31:35 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/36chor-and-robin-read-us-bj-novak/</guid>
      <description>The New Deal in Jordan&amp;#39;s room by POLIW.AT 930AM
robin read Jack and I Sofia a short story by bj novak =-=-=-=-=-=&amp;ndash;==-=-=-==&amp;ndash;==&amp;ndash;==-=&amp;ndash;==-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=
chbs we&amp;rsquo;re going through my dying process.
starts with the show
the last show
the encore
dying in the encore
no its a hallucination of my dying process, in it is a tour of humanity
and everything in between
chbs
[1] a show [2] architecture [3] art [4]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Youre Fred Its Real</title>
      <link>/post/if-youre-fred-its-real/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 10:29:13 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/if-youre-fred-its-real/</guid>
      <description>im on mission
its a huge tasks
mistakes are okay
igf im learning or growing
my mantra
listen
-=-==&amp;ndash;=-==&amp;ndash;=-=
acoustic mic i spent alll this time recording and i dont listen  (v2)
I spent all this time recording (8) I did it all without listening (8.5)  1142AM
ok ok ok ok ok ok
at cole coffee with Robin, we get to work on our own shit then we have to rehearse the rest of the day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Mixx With Diego Rivera</title>
      <link>/post/learning-mixx-with-diego-rivera/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jan 2019 12:58:20 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/learning-mixx-with-diego-rivera/</guid>
      <description>1258 PM
@ camTedGus&amp;rsquo;s apartment. I&amp;rsquo;m cleaned up a bit! Just could use a haircut lol.
Making some french press coffee, spent the morning paying off my sleep debt then learning Mixx, I started learning Resolume but couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out how to turn the audio clip of a robot saying the name of the software every minute or so. Super annoying! But mixx I have been ab
music for every hour of the day</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frobin Hit Pond Field River by Moonlight</title>
      <link>/post/fred-and-robin-hit-pond-field-river-by-moonlight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 04:39:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/fred-and-robin-hit-pond-field-river-by-moonlight/</guid>
      <description>444AM
next time I go out I teach God a lesson next time I go out I teach God a lesson gotta lesson from the trappist abbott every actor an object of art said in the word of God the pen of benedict is it a creed or creep when he too vague to beg gotta lesson from the drunk shaman mantra of a thousand as of late they my therapy today I need it I breath it a clean slate pero slate lake stop crying over lost tape a la carte trip visit from edos suddenly I a monk handsome youth having fun god chose my temple he chose the sword I chose the pen and his temple well tortured to death theres snow on his sleeve I&#39;ll make a plan to fuck for a living believe wouldn&#39;t&#39; you these discoveries my discoveries bother the bishop cause I gotta lesson cant believe I sayin this but I couldnt keep my shit together I had to ruin it plow it way matt shave his head on the beat cant read kramer kick open that door cosbypolitics on the floor cause next time I go out I teach God a lesson next time I go out I teach god a lesson next time I go out I teach god a lesson too you call me in my own headphones  922 am tree is dying we still climbed it moonlit our faces god test it pond so cold we still test it she ate a chip off my leg reinstate became the cig bank i think too much therefore Im too much I tka her to write her affairs I write my side of field I hope it works in the shield its dope I think its working who knows i quit smoking cept always writing, riding eception only my music these days seem to be only person that gets me dont care anyways i calling the shots my house my rules get out this the no phone zone this the go the fuck home zone this the only way to spoon though so my leg don&#39;t fall asleep I sorry I meant it don&#39;t eat that corndog brian this time jack next time pero is going to see me fuck by the end of the scene go pro ok 4k england brixton difference go head add it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Round and Dampy Had a Bad Set</title>
      <link>/post/round-and-dampy-had-a-bad-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2019 10:15:30 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/round-and-dampy-had-a-bad-set/</guid>
      <description>vina CA
12 pm
in the car with helen josh brian and jack&amp;rsquo;s driving
he rented the car and we&amp;rsquo;re heading to vina to tour some monastery
I got audio of WAIT ROBIN IS WATCHING ME WTF
I can&amp;rsquo;t type what I normally type when she&amp;rsquo;s watching. I&amp;rsquo;ll try to change the angle.
I love her our scenes are amazing
from running through
1227 pm
rehearsals are going well evem in the car, we do a couple scenes then sing to a nice loud song as a break.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Therapy Couch</title>
      <link>/post/therapy-couch/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jan 2019 23:19:37 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/therapy-couch/</guid>
      <description>1119 pm
listening to poetics 2 rehearsal tape.
[[ paleblue beatz despression ]] well i already made all the music for the entire planet the therapy couch taught me by taking me by hand  getting a set together for the 6th, going to Vina tomorrow to tour everything monk life
ch 36: my final scene, the person is led to believe that it&amp;rsquo;s not my last scene, but Im behaving as if its my last scene chamber 36 my final scene something about it bein my last that being important</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paleo Pancakes Offline but Online</title>
      <link>/post/paleo-pancakes-offline-but-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 09:29:34 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/paleo-pancakes-offline-but-online/</guid>
      <description>929am
brianna made paleo pancakes
today I feel a little less talented aha
I am really letting money get to my mind for some reason
I need to just work it out :)
I know what I have to do, and I know what it&amp;rsquo;s going to take. =&amp;ndash;=-==&amp;ndash;==-==-=&amp;ndash;==&amp;ndash;=-=-=-=-=-==-=-=&amp;ndash;==-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=
hmm what do I do&amp;hellip;. I guess I know what to do..
I need to make a poliwat site and pale blue site with dope audio links</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slow the World Down Thinkpad Senior Sitting Next to Me</title>
      <link>/post/slow-the-world-down-thinkpad-senior-sitting-next-to-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2019 10:12:46 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/slow-the-world-down-thinkpad-senior-sitting-next-to-me/</guid>
      <description>1015AM wednesday jan 23rd 2k19 @ Mars of Venus (Davis.Coffeeshop)
What the people are saying: &amp;ldquo;&amp;rdquo;&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt;because we have an international fucking audience, that&amp;rsquo;s why
 international students as well
some of whom we want to get involved
calls from the coffee shop
I got some info for you
{then a classic move if this is to happen, it should go to you}
 &amp;rdquo;&amp;ldquo;&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt;cause I&amp;rsquo;m more patient or whatever, doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birth of Poliwat 2.09</title>
      <link>/post/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hello/</guid>
      <description>Lunar Particle Syntax
oh and don&amp;rsquo;t trust anything on reddit
tuesday0414pm01222k19
holy shit.
I got the laptop!!!!
I&amp;rsquo;m in heaven
also we&amp;rsquo;ve had a lot of sex since bri drove an hour just to pick me up from the BART station.
it was tight.
IM BACK !!!! Holy shit it feels great. I can&amp;rsquo;t stop
@ a coffee shop now in Davis, it&amp;rsquo;s nice but I don&amp;rsquo;t remember the name of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/showcase/</guid>
      <description>Living Songbook Master Document Debut album  life is a sacred circle check I am a spliff check World My stage check g my g check I index from 0 check internet will not be homogenized You already know She Breaking Glass Ceiling check Trapt in the womb check  Album 2 =-=-==&amp;ndash;==-=-=-=&amp;ndash;=-==&amp;ndash;=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-==-= Song list master: (poliwat formal tracks, then type beats)
Type Beats  - bipolar mixed features type beat  each song roughly looks like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>New music everyday so help me God
&amp;gt; This site is my brain dump 
&amp;gt; This site helps me write songs 
&amp;gt; This site is my Yin 
This site is a my safe space &amp;gt;This site is my social media
&amp;gt;This site is my social media
&amp;gt; This site is my Yang 
&amp;gt; This site is not spellchecked 
&amp;gt; This site allows me to go crazy, and always come back down.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>